Previously on Sterling Point…
Is there anything I can do to help you?
Take that box of shit
Gord's been hoarding to the thrift store.
Is this Mom's stuff?
I know you're sick of that song
'cause I've played it 1.000 times.
As much as I love that song. it is nothing
compared to how much I love you. Joe.
It sounds like from the tape
that you guys were dating?
Ellis. do you have a gift for the thing
at Ramona's tonight?
- What?
- You need to get Annie something.
- Where'd you sleep?
- Oona's.
Do you guys
have a vibe or something?
Sorry. this is the beautiful
Stacey Mallory.
Hi.
- You think you like her?
- Why?
- No reason.
- Are you jealous?
Oona!
Well. this is the porch.
I'm gonna kiss you.
Hey. where's your sister?
If you think she might have fled
to Canada. you might be not high.
I am going up there.
Dude. no. Do not do that.
She's really mad.
I know. That's why I gotta go up there.
Okay. fine. I will go out there
and fix this for you.
- Oh. my God.
- Sorry. what the fuck are you doing here?
Grandpappy left the island to us too.
So now it's a threesome. guys.
Let's fucking sell this bitch.
I see resort vibes.
I see… I see water bungalows.
I see ateliers.
I see selling a million tiny little houses
and making a million tiny fortunes.
Is his off button. like… Where is it?
Does he have…
Connor. we are not selling this island.
Quiet. I have 20-20 hearing.
We won't sell it today. but when we're 18.
- Yeah. but don't you turn 18 soon?
- Yeah. Big party. You're invited. Sis.
- I'm gonna freak out! This is...
- I know. You can't…
Two-thirds majority. so…
It's irrelevant 'cause
I won't do what she doesn't want.
Thank you.
Please begin the long journey
to acceptance now.
because this will never be a Four Seasons.
it will never be an Erewhon.
It'll remain a really magical island
we can come to with our children
for the rest of our lives.
as our grandpa and dead mother intended.
- Or...
- No!
I'm feeling a little bullied.
Mom loved this place. Connor.
Being here is like being near her.
Can't you fucking feel that for a second?
No. Emotions will get in the way
of my business sense.
- You don't have a business sense.
- Oh.
Okay. little Miss
"I wanna go to Wharton like Daddy."
Why don't you pitch to me
why we should make memories
instead of making millions?
I literally could.
- You want me to pitch it right now?
- Yeah.
I'd like a little more time to prepare.
I usually do a PowerPoint.
Going to business school. You'll do great.
Great. Fine. I'm happy to.
Tired of searching for subtitles?
Ray generates them instantly: getray.app
There are… a lot of beautiful women here.
Beautiful people are everywhere.
God is good.
- I'm gonna jump off a bridge.
- There's great boating.
Lots of fresh vegetables.
And there's zucchini and squash.
- Yep. Uh…
- Zucchini is squash.
- Ramona. There's also...
- Yeah. Thinking. Um…
- Clean water.
- There's clean water!
And. uh. loons. which are cute.
- And cliff jumping.
- Cliff jumping.
- And…
- Yeah.
There's old photos of Mom.
and her old things.
I mean. Connor. dude.
memories have no price tag.
- Oh. man. Sis. I'm…
- Yeah. doesn't it touch you?
I'm really not trying to be mean
right now. but…
you flopped.
That was really bad. and I'm sorry.
and I'm starting to see
why you didn't get into
the business school program.
- Oh.
- I…
I shouldn't have done that to you.
That was on me. I was cruel.
You know what. Connor?
Fine. I see where you're coming from.
Why don't you just spend.
like. one week here.
and if you hate it.
if you totally don't get it.
we can have a serious conversation
about the possibility of selling.
Uh. yeah. I need a minute
to think about my decision.
Sorry. Just gonna steal you
for one quick second.
What's wrong with you?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I'm lying.
- You're lying?
- Obviously. I just wanted him to shut up.
Oh. I'm impressed. It was good.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Can't believe I said "thank you" to that.
- Mmm.
He'll fall in love with a girl here
and wanna stay anyway.
- It's happened on all of our vacations.
- Okay.
- Or a bear will eat him.
- Oh!
- Wolf.
- Or a wolf will eat him.
Connor! The offer pumpkins
in five. four. three. two.
- one.
- Take me to the cliffs.
Deal. So deal. Let's go.
How tall are the cliffs. and will there
be wolves? Can we confirm or deny?
I would do
less talking and more walking.
Also. where's my room?
Hello?
Hi. I'm looking to speak with
Joseph Anderson. please.
He's not here right now.
Could you have him call me back?
My name is Marjorie Lewis.
Gordon Campbell's estate lawyer.
Okay.
Actually. do you happen to have
a contact number for a Ramona Campbell?
- Uh. no. I don't. Sorry.
- Okay.
Please let Mr. Anderson know I called.
Yeah. Will do.
- You okay? Who was that?
- Yeah.
Just someone for Dad.
- So I'll see you later for dinner?
- Yeah.
Speak brutal truths.
This is unreal.
Amazing work.
"Unreal?" "Amazing?" Really?
I'm going for perfection!
So I'm gonna go try again.
- It's perfect.
- Don't lie to me.
- He doesn't know how talented... Hey!
- Oh. hey.
- What's up?
- We are beaver tail tasting.
I'm glad you're here. actually.
I wanted to get in your head a little bit.
Understand why you decided bringing Annie
a lamp was the big romantic move.
Are you trying to be her boyfriend
or her electrician?
- Yeah.
- Good one. Maple.
Either way. she was fully making out
with Rory when I got there. so…
Okay. no. No. no. no. Ellis.
Ellis. look at me. You are hot. Okay?
Accept it. Own it. Live in it.
Bro. she likes you. It's so obvious.
Don't let the soft-boy
love bomber interfere.
Ask her to the movie thing.
Just do something. please.
Perfect. Look alive.
- Hi.
- Hey. guys.
- Hey.
- Hey. Hi.
Okay. then. I will introduce myself.
I am Annie's fraternal
twin brother. Connor.
- Apologies in advance.
- She's always been the funny one. right?
I'm sure you already know this.
All right. this looks really good.
I'm in no mood to break my neck today.
but we are going cliff jumping. so…
- We'll explain why later.
- I'm. like. excited.
Or nervous-excited
kind of a thing.
Ugh! You chew so loud. Please come.
Yeah. yeah. no. I'm always down.
- Yeah. Kinda famous for flips.
- Don't let her flip.
- Got it.
- Guys!
Are you coming?
Uh. yeah. Mmm-hmm.
Great.
Hey. uh. Ramona? Sorry. Um…
- Can I talk to you for a sec?
- Yeah. Oh.
- Seriously? Outside? Okay.
- Just… Yeah.
What the fuck
is this delicious soft thing?
It's a beaver tail.
Okay. what is going on?
Gordon's lawyer's looking for you?
She called the house.
- And?
- Why is she looking for you?
- Why does she wanna talk to my dad?
- I don't know. Ask him.
Ramona.
Look. when people die. there's gonna be
lawyers making calls and paperwork.
I don't know. It's annoying. Sorry.
Is it about the island?
- It's fine.
- Is it?
Um…
Okay. so. apparently. I…
I own it with Annie and Connor.
Like. a three-way split shit situation.
- But I'm handling it. okay?
- What?
Relax. Annie promised me
she's gonna do whatever I want.
and I'm obviously not selling.
so we're good.
- What? Connor? Pull up.
- Is that Rory? Damn. man.
What the hell?
What is going on? So good to see you. man.
Rory. my man. looking fine as hell.
Thank you. man.
Connor. I'm sorry. You're glowing.
What is this?
This humidity is so good on you.
The humidity is great for my skin.
I look my best when I'm in the Bahamas.
and apparently Canada?
Okay. well. look. just get in. loser.
I wanna show you around.
Oh. baby. take me to the cliffs.
To the cliffs? Yes! I love the cliffs.
Where… What are the cliffs?
A cliff is. like. a sheer rock formation.
It has water at the bottom. sometimes not.
I only recommend jumping when there is.
- Put in "cliffs."
- We're going to Cliff's house?
- Male fuckery is so interesting.
- Kind of a red flag that they're friends.
This is beyond me. So. I'm out.
- Oh. okay.
- Bye.
Have fun with Sully.
Cliffs. Let's go to the cliffs.
Hey.
- Hey.
Thank you so much for fixing that lamp.
It really meant a lot to me. so…
It's also so cool that you can do that.
Fix lamps.
Yeah. no...
Jacobson. get in.
You gonna come?
Uh. I can't. I have a bunch of
rich people's boats to clean. So…
Sorry. Um…
Well. I'll see you later. maybe?
- Yeah. Okay.
- Okay.
Hey. um. have you seen Teen Wolf
or Uptown Girls?
- You mean my two favorite movies?
- Really?
- No. I'm sorry. I have not seen either.
- Oh. neither. Wow.
Yeah. I am a hundred years behind
on movies. It's not a great situation.
God. no. Never having seen Uptown Girls
is diabolical.
- I'm sad for you. honestly. It's crazy.
- That's extreme. okay?
There's this outdoor double-feature thing.
They do it every summer.
- It's actually pretty fun.
- Cool.
Would you wanna go?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. That sounds so much fun.
- Yeah.
It's actually perfect. 'cause I'm trying
to get Connor not to hate this place.
and he's weirdly obsessed
with Dakota Fanning.
- Yo. Annie!
- Yeah. awesome.
Totally meant it as a group thing.
Okay. Okay!
- Uh. see you?
- Yeah.
- See ya. Bye.
- Bye.
All right.
who's ready for the cliffs?
Bye. Ellis.
Okay.
- Everybody's up here.
- Okay. Okay.
- Oh. my God!
- Yeah!
- Okay.
- Whoo!
Oh. my God.
Okay.
Yeah! That was fun.
Maybe wanna look first.
- Okay.
Yeah!
Annie!
You guys coming down?
- Okay. So...
- No. no. no. I can't.
You're not supposed to look
before you leap.
- Isn't that exactly what you should do?
- Do it!
My stomach hurts.
Your hesitation is your intelligence.
This is actually so dangerous.
So this is your brain going.
"I'm smarter than all these people."
- "I won't take that risk."
- That's exactly it. Thank you for that.
- Yeah.
My mom used to jump off these cliffs.
but I am clearly not as chill as she was.
Oh. don't say that. You are.
- I accept this.
- I wanna show something. Can I?
Come on. We'll catch ya.
I'm sort of nervous
to leave Connor on his own.
I fucking love nature! Oh. my God!
Uh…
I think he'll be good.
He seems good.
Come on.
Cowards!
Whoo!
- Know what'd make it easier?
- What?
A water slide. A really slippery one.
You know we don't own these cliffs. right?
- We could.
- No. No. we couldn't.
Can someone help me with this?
- Oh! Dibs! Dibs! Dibs!
- No!
No. I got it. I got you.
Okay.
- Oh. my God.
- Thank you.
Okay.
Thank you.
Yeah. for sure.
- Like. you need to shut up.
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean it.
Yeah. okay. I'm coming.
Karim. are you a fucking comedian?
Is this a joke?
6.5? That's highway robbery.
The land alone is worth
way more than that. and you know it.
Tell them to come back with something real
because they are wasting my time. Karim.
Bye.
Ugh! Realtors.
Do we need a new one?
Uh. no. no. Just a few new wires.
She's good to go.
Oh. boo. I was kind of hoping
for a new boat.
This one's. you know…
- Am I right?
- Yeah. Right.
- Okay. well. your total comes up to…
- Okay.
…um. $450.
You have my Amex on file. right?
Sorry. we're actually cash-only now.
- Oh. wow.
- Yeah.
- People still use cash. huh?
- They do.
You're in luck.
Rory just got me some for the cleaners.
Says I gotta start tipping them now.
What did you say that was again?
$650. right?
- Uh. yeah. Yeah.
- Okay.
All right. I'll be right back.
Cool.
- So. when are you gonna tell her?
- Sorry?
Ah. I knew it.
Still in the "holding long. deep.
meaningful gaze.
but not talking about it" phase.
- What?
- And we feel a little hurt about that.
- A little "ouch."
- We don't feel any way about that because…
she's into this girl
named Stacey Mallory. so…
- Stacey Mallory? I'm sorry. Just pick one.
- Yeah. just pick one.
Yeah.
I always knew I had twin telepathy.
We're not twins.
Whatever. It's undeniable.
You're in love.
No. I'm not.
You're in denial.
Yeah. maybe.
'Cause she's my best friend. but…
Oona doesn't. like. date people. anyway.
She gives them the best two weeks
of their lives and then dips.
So. she's avoidant attached.
We can work through that.
You know what they say. "Love is love."
Yeah. Yeah. they do say that.
Have you seen Love on the Spectrum?
It's really sweet.
- This is so cool.
- I know.
I was always so intimidated by you.
- By me?
- Yes.
- No. you were not.
- I was.
Why? You were cooler than everyone.
You were playing piano
at Carnegie Hall at eight.
I was seven.
I'm so sorry. Seven.
You smoked cigarettes. and you rode
the subways in. like. middle school.
- You were on Ellen.
- I was.
That was. like. peak time to be on Ellen.
Why did you stop playing?
It involved a car door
and my little cousin
slamming my hand into it.
- Oh. my God.
- The kicker is. it didn't heal right. So…
I can't play-play ever again.
- I'm really sorry. It's really hard.
- No. No. it's okay.
Okay.
- Saunas.
- Hmm.
Saunas are great for anxiety.
Is it just that they make you
so fucking hot
you can't think of anything but not dying?
- Are you too hot?
- No. I'm not. I'm kidding.
You look pretty hot.
I could do this all day. Jacobson.
Okay. You win. I'm gonna…
How are you doing?
- Cooler.
- Come on. I mean about…
being here.
Ramona and…
your mom.
- Oh. that.
- That.
- Hmm. Uh…
- Mmm.
I honestly just never thought
I was that affected by having a dead mom.
Which sounds so bad to say. but. um…
I didn't know her. you know?
But then being here. it's like…
"Oh!"
"Is having a dead mom the thing
that fucked me up the most?"
So. yeah. just being here with Ramona
and this place. it's like…
you know. "What would it have been like
to grow up with all…"
It's like. I just can't get my head
to stop going down
the rabbit hole of. like…
"What if all of this
had been mine as a kid?"
"What if my mom lived?"
"Who would I be?" So…
Yeah. I'm just feeling like…
Feeling all of that for the first time.
Like. "Oh! Holy shit. My mom is dead."
"I don't have a… mom."
- I'm sorry. That's...
- No. I'm sorry.
No. What? Why are you sorry?
I… No. I just… I…
♪ Killed the vibe ♪
- No. you didn't. You did not.
- Yes. I did. I killed the moment.
I did. I did.
I fucking hate you feeling the need
to say sorry just because you have…
feelings.
You shouldn't feel like that.
Okay?
- Ooh.
- That was…
That's so embarrassing.
Okay. See. I think
that's just a sign we need to go.
- Okay.
- All right. Fine.
- Okay. Yeah.
- Ooh! Two skips.
- Not bad.
- Whatever. whatever.
- How many did you get?
- Wait.
I wanna ask you
about the property values here.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Okay. so I know that I always fall asleep
during movies.
um. but would you wanna
go to that cinema thing tomorrow?
Like. together?
No. Separately.
- Oh. okay.
- Yes. Together.
Um…
Yeah. Yeah. I'd love to.
Okay. Great.
Love.
Yeah.
Yeah. "love." I… Yeah.
Hi.
- You good?
- Mmm-hmm.
Wait. where's Connor? Did he leave?
Yeah. he realized we only have
a composting toilet.
- So he went to Rory's.
- Oh.
Thought maybe
you'd spend the night there too.
What?
Nothing.
Um… No. nothing. Just. Rory is like...
Rich and dissociated?
Stop. No. he's nice and clear.
and. like. really likes me.
which is insane to me.
Can I ask you a personal question?
You ask me literally
the most personal questions
- seventy-eight times a day.
- Okay.
- Can I?
- Go for it.
When did you know that you were gay?
I don't know.
I kind of always knew. I guess.
Really?
- Why?
- It sounds so weird. I guess I kinda…
thought that I was asexual until. like…
right now.
Really?
Yeah. I was just never interested
in sex at all.
Maybe 'cause I had a gay boyfriend.
Maybe that's why I had a gay boyfriend.
Let's unpack that later.
Then you banged Rory.
- and you're obsessed.
- Ramona!
No. I did not.
I did not. and I never…
Wait. you've never?
Okay. It's so sweet that you think
there's a world in which I have had sex.
- Really sweet.
- I just assumed everyone in New York
has sex all the time. everywhere.
Yeah. just. like. on the subway.
Or the fire escapes.
You're gonna be so disappointed
when you visit.
Have you?
Had sex on a fire escape before?
No.
Come on.
No. I haven't. It's…
I don't know.
being hot isn't exactly my brand.
Isn't being hot. like.
literally your whole brand?
No! No.
I'm sorry. I just find it hard to believe
that girls aren't freaking out over you.
Yeah. they aren't. though.
Ugh. I wish you could see yourself
the way I do.
Ew. Incest. Gross.
You know what I mean. I missed.
What the fuck?
No! No!
- Ow!
- Sorry.
Oona kinda asked me
to go to the movies with her tomorrow.
Like. a date?
I don't know.
Okay. so then it's obviously a date.
- That's so exciting.
- No. that makes no sense.
It does. It's a scientific fact.
If you don't know for sure it's a date.
it definitely is.
She probably just meant it as friends.
"She probably meant it as friends."
- Shut up!
- You're blushing.
- I'm not.
- God. you're blushing.
Stop! Give me my book back.
I'm trying to re-read it by morning.
Sorry. sorry. sorry.
- Blushing.
- Stop!
Do you wanna go
to that movie thing tonight?
No. Let's just put something on
in the theater here.
Cool.
Honestly. I need a break from Annie.
Annie is going?
Yeah. Ellis invited her.
Ellis? Is that that kid
who's been ripping me off?
- What?
Just a bit here and there.
Mom. that's fucked up.
Honey. your dad hasn't paid taxes
in 15 years.
- Wait. what?
- This Sancerre. by the way.
it's so crisp.
God. your dad raised you right.
I bet you got his business sense too.
I do have his business sense.
When the time comes to sell that island.
you know who to call.
My girl. Denise. Duh.
- Duh.
- You know what?
I am gonna go to that movie.
Fine. I'll come too.
Oh. Denise. would you like to join us?
No. honey. I hate seeing movies
with a big group of people.
You're so right.
That is the worst way to watch them.
Isn't it? You boys have fun.
Okay.
What the fuck?
Why are you trying on so many things
to lay on the ground and watch a movie?
Because I just… I don't wanna be cold.
- Are you coming tonight?
- No. I'm on the last chapter.
I need to find out what the score is
and where in the body it's being kept.
Okay. Suit yourself.
We're gonna miss you.
You know.
you need to be careful with Ramona.
Sorry. what?
You can't treat her like every random girl
you barely know.
I've genuinely got no idea
what you're talking about.
Yes. you do.
Look. she's. like. your best friend.
And if you're gonna go on a date.
then you've got to take it...
No. we're not going on a date.
There's no vibe like that between us.
- Oona. you're already doing it.
- What?
What am I doing?
Like. breaking her heart.
Yeah. well. she turned a date
into a group hang.
- so message received. I guess?
- A date?
Bitch. she doesn't even know
you're remotely interested.
Hey. Hey. here's an idea for you.
Have you ever tried telling her.
"I like you"?
- No. Who says… No one says that.
- Rory does!
Boys like Rory do.
They listen to Brené Brown
and say what they feel. and it works.
And as much as I love repressed guys
who are really good with their hands.
you all can be pretty hard to read.
These need more powdered sugar.
Hey.
Hey. Hey. babe.
- I didn't know you were coming.
- Um…
Yeah. no. I'm…
I'm. like. a real cinephile.
Love movies.
I never fall asleep watching them.
You wanna get some food?
Yep. Yeah.
I'm starving. actually. so… Perfect.
You ready?
Tonight's the night. You gotta wife her.
- Gotta wife her up.
- Mmm. Yep.
Connor!
Connor.
Are you plying our underage sister
with alcohol?
- I'm underage too. Relax.
- There's kids here.
I have to let this sink in. what.
30 minutes? Fifteen? How long?
- Wait. Have you never had a drink?
- No. I'm not cool.
- I wasn't judging. Got it.
- Yeah.
- When does wifey get here?
- Like. should have been ten minutes ago.
But she's always late. so it's fine.
Hey. oh. maybe we should slow down a bit?
I think it's a good time
to go see Uptown Girls.
So true. So true.
Dakota Fanning?
- Beautifully precocious.
- So precocious.
- Can we get cotton candy?
- Can I take the flask. please?
Hey.
Um. wanna do something lame?
Don't move. please.
- Yeah. No. we're good. Sorry.
- Sorry.
Yeah. we're good.
- Actually. stop. stop.
- You stop.
- No. I'm not doing anything. Sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Guys. can we do this?
- Sorry.
- Okay. we got it.
- We got it.
Okay. We all got it.
I really like…
being near you.
I really like being near you too.
What?
Nothing.
- What?
- Nothing.
Dude. look at that. These goddamn kids.
- Yo!
- What?
That's not chill.
Dude. I think we're beyond
being threatened as a species.
You'll be threatened when they fuck.
Now I'm gonna go throw some peaches.
I'll peach it up.
Oh!
Well. there's just nothing like good help.
I love this scene.
It's very cute
you like this movie so much.
You know what's crazy?
If I close one…
If I close one eye like this.
I can see three Dakota Fannings.
I love that.
- God. you were so right.
- Mmm-hmm.
Getting drunk kind of fucks.
Like. here I am.
stood up by my best friend.
love of my life... like. that's a wifey.
And I feel…
nothing.
And let me tell you. that fucks.
- Feeling nothing is the goal.
- Goal in life.
God. you're so smart.
Annie would fucking have an aneurysm
if she heard you.
I love being on the water.
I love floating.
This is my safe space. Right here.
God. I have to pee again. Geez.
Alcohol is a diuretic.
I don't know what that means.
God. they need to make
more movies like this.
Wonderful. girls.
I've never seen
the film before this.
- Mmm. Really?
- Yeah.
I think I tried to watch it last time.
but then I just fell asleep.
And then I woke up after everyone had gone
and never woke me up.
- Yeah.
- That sucks.
This is cooler. Wow.
Sully is a god.
- This is the best thing I've...
- Hey!
Stacey Mallory!
- God! Good to see you.
- Hey. Ramona.
You're drunk.
- No. I'm not.
- Yeah.
Yeah. you're an alcoholic for love.
That's called "a love addict." which is
honestly real and can be super dark.
My cousin had to go to...
I don't fucking care about your cousin.
Who's your cousin?
- Let me ask you a question.
- Okay. Ramona. stop.
Have you ever even been with a girl?
Have you ever dated a girl?
You've never dated a girl.
Have you ever dated anybody?
In 39 hours. she'll lose interest
'cause she does this
with fucking everyone.
And you'll go back
to fucking John or Derek...
- Ramona. stop. bro. You're being mean.
- "You're being mean."
Especially though you got two first names.
which I know you think is so cool.
- Okay. I'm gonna go. Good night.
- So cool. by the way.
- You're not. and you never will be.
- Wait.
Bye!
- Drink some water and then go home.
- No. No.
Stacey Mallory!
Oona! Wait!
Sorry. guys. Sorry.
- What are you doing?
- Sorry.
- Are you okay?
- God. she really is fast.
What is happening? What is wrong with you?
Why are you acting like this?
We were just eating.
You fucked with me. It's...
I didn't fuck with you.
Yes. you did.
You…
You asked me to come here. like. with you.
Together.
Yeah. We do everything together.
I don't know. I just thought…
I thought it'd be different
because of the thing at the party.
What thing?
Ramona. don't.
You didn't want to?
'Cause it seemed like you did.
No.
Okay. Got it.
Okay.
- How have you never seen this?
- No. I'm not saying…
It's clearly incredible.
- Can I have some? Thanks.
- Yeah. Sorry.
- No. it's okay.
- Hey.
Hey.
- How you doing? Hey. man.
- Hey-yo.
- Cheers. my boy.
Hola.
What's good?
This is cute. huh?
- Yeah. Really cute.
- Nice.
- Really cute.
- Never seen it like this.
I'm looking forward to when they put
Teen Wolf on.
I've not seen that yet.
You guys seen Teen Wolf?
- No. actually.
- No.
Ellis?
What?
- Have you seen Teen Wolf?
- What?
Uh. no.
God. let's go. So this is
our first viewing of Teen Wolf together.
Yo. Six orders of. uh. poutine
and some wings.
- And grab yourself a treat if you want.
- Whoa!
Fucking…
What the fuck?
I said he could get a treat.
You're such an asshole. Lincoln.
- I'm just…
- I'm gonna go find Ramona.
No. no.
Ellis. I'm sorry. He's drunk.
- He's...
- Yo. you forgot my card.
- I'm sorry.
- Why are you sorry? I'm hungry. bro.
Wah-wah.
Fuck.
It's good. Take it easy. man.
Why are you freaking out all the time?
Why do you have to do shit like that?
You suck. you suck.
and you suck. you suck.
And you. Eloise.
I'm really fucking proud of you. man.
You've gotten so good in an hour.
You got big things ahead of you.
You good. Ramona?
Excuse you.
What?
You sneezed. Excuse you.
Hey. what's going on?
I'm dominating frogs.
Mayor of Frogville over here.
What? No. I mean Ramona. Is she okay?
Yeah. she's resting.
Why did you let her drink so much?
Jesus Christ. Connor.
Chill the fuck out. man.
She's had a rough week.
- What is wrong with you? I wanna know.
- Am I dead?
Okay. let's get you home.
Play one more game.
I really need to get that dolphin.
- He doesn't wanna stay. He wants to come.
- I'm so fucking mad at you now.
- You're always mad at me.
- Can you come. please?
- No fighting.
- We got it. Got it.
- Your pants are falling down.
- Get her pants.
I love you guys.
We love you too.
Oh. you smell like…
Let's get you up.
Okay. can you wake up for me? Yeah. yeah.
- Bumblebee.
- No. I have the bumblebee.
Everything's gonna be okay.
- It's all right.
- Okay.
- I got you.
- Okay. Big step. Careful. careful.
Jesus!
- Stop screaming.
- What the hell is going on?
Nothing. Just…
I had the worst night
of my young adult life. actually.
It was awful. Annie and Connor...
They rock. though. They rock!
They ruled. Is that a song?
I think that's… Wait. no. that's…
Ellis. do me a favor. Set up the couch
for her. She'll spend the night with us.
Wait. No. No. no. no.
I'm dying in my own bed.
You're not gonna die.
We'll get her home safe. She'll be fine.
- Ellis. you got her? It's all good.
- Yeah. Got her.
Annie. make sure you bring
the hedgehog back up. And leave the bee.
- He's scaring me a little.
- Yeah. okay.
Also. do not forget the frog.
I am deeply attached to him.
He has very sad eyes.
Yep. I got it. Connor! Thank you.
All right. good night.
So. this is how y'all do it
in New York City?
- Uh. what do you mean?
- Why'd you let her drink so much?
I… No. I'm sorry. I really didn't…
It was my brother and I'm furious...
Damn it. You're supposed to be
looking out for her.
- I am looking out for her.
- It's exactly what Gordon was afraid of.
Excuse me?
No. Tell me what Gordon was afraid of.
That Ramona's New York City siblings
would come corrupt her?
Is that why he kept us apart?
- I'm curious.
- That's not what I said.
Do you honestly expect me to believe
that you didn't see my mom for years
even though you lived here
and she lived there.
- and she was dying of cancer?
- Annie. it was just…
- It was complicated then. okay?
- What? What was complicated?
- It's not my place.
- To what?
To tell you how she died.
What did you just say?
She died giving birth…
to Ramona.
No. she didn't. She died of cancer.
How do you know that?
Because I was there.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today